So anything I say now is making a scene
You used to say my sister was too bossy
And only I needed you the most
Now that Fu Chenzhou is the heir
And my sister became Mrs Fu
You regret it
Gu Chengze
You didn't like me that much after all
Enough
If you hadn't acted so recklessly
The Fu Group wouldn't be
so disgusted with the Gu family
If you had signed the share authorization earlier
The Gu Group wouldn't be so passive
What are you looking at
Nothing
Gu Chengze and Su Yuyao
I'm not worried
Just thinking that a position you fight for
isn't so secure after all
But that's none of my business anymore
I liked what you just said
Which part